[{"Question": "Name a part of the body that's hard to keep a band aid stuck to", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Finger",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Elbow",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Knee",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Toe",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Palm",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Foot",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation in which a man would meet a lot of women", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Physician",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Hairdresser",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Salesperson",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Bartender",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Nurse",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Lifeguard",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "What was the first important decision you ever made?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Marriage",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "College",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Job",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Leave Home",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Buy House",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something men buy in a men's store that they don't try on", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Tie",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Socks",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Underwear",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Scarf",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Belt",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides balls, name something a juggler might juggle", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bowling Pins",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Fruit",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Knives",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Plates",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Rings",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "When something goes wrong with your car, who do you call first?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 60
},
{"name": "Garage",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Father",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Friend",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "AAA",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name the best Christmas gift you ever received as a young kid", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bicycle",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Doll",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Train Set",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Ice Skates",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Stereo",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where you would see a lot of mirrors", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Fun House",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Beauty Salon",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Dressing Room",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Bathroom",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Clothing Store",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Dance Studio",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something bad a person might do on the first day of a new job", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Show Up Late",
"votes": 69
},
{"name": "Wear Wrong Clothes",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Make A Mistake",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Take Long Lunch",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Gossip",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Leave Early",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a president who fought in a war", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Dwight Eisenhower",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "George Washington",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "George Bush",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "John F. Kennedy",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Ulysses S. Grant",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Teddy Roosevelt",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something imported from Germany", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Beer",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Cars",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Clocks",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Chocolate",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Hummel Figures",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that the sun does", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Shines",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "Gives off Heat",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Sets",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Rises",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Burns Skin",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Revolves",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people stay home to wait for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Telephone Call",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Repairman",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Mail",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Deliveries",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Guests",
"votes": 10
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place in a city where you'd generally find a taxi", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Airport",
"votes": 46
},
{"name": "Hotel",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Busy Street",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Bus Station",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Shopping Mall",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Train Station",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you buy salted", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Nuts",
"votes": 76
},
{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Pretzels",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Potato Chips",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Pork",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an ingredient in a good bowl of chili", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Meat",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Beans",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Chili Powder",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Tomatoes",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Hot Peppers",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Onion",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a woman never travels without", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Makeup",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Purse",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Credit Cards",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hair Dryer",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something kids ask for at amusement parks", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cotton Candy",
"votes": 74
},
{"name": "Balloons",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Hot Dog",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Soda",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Stuffed Animal",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that a teacher threatens unruly students with", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Detention",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "Principal's Office",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Extra Homework",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "No Recess",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Spank",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Tell Their Parents",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you'd find at the bottom of a woman's purse", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Money",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Makeup",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Keys",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Pins",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Tissue",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Nail File",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where you see adults carrying sleeping children", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Mall",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Fair",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Church",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Movie",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Airport",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Zoo",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that's hard to refold other than a tablecloth", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Map",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "Sheets",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Tent",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Parachute",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Blanket",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name the most famous newscaster in the United States", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Walter Cronkite",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Dan Rather",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Peter Jennings",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Tom Brokaw",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Ted Koppel",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Barbara Walters",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a sport a lot of people think is fixed", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Wrestling",
"votes": 46
},
{"name": "Boxing",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Horse Racing",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Football",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Basketball",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something kids talk about", 
"Answers": [{"name": "School",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Games",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Sports",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Music",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Parents",
"votes": 8
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something specific that a dentist does to your teeth", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cleans",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Drills",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Fills",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "X Rays",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Flosses",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Pulls",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you wish you had in your backyard", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Pool",
"votes": 82
},
{"name": "Hot Tub",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Flowers",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Swing",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Trees",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that can give you blisters", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Shoes",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Gardening",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Shoveling",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Burns",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Sweeping",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an indication that a baby isn't feeling well", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Crying",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Fever",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Fussy",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Throw Up",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Listless",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a famous character with 'Kid' in his name", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Billy The Kid",
"votes": 87
},
{"name": "Karate Kid",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Captain Kidd",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Cisco Kid",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Sundance Kid",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occasion when a man might be especially nervous", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Wedding Day",
"votes": 69
},
{"name": "Marriage Proposal",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Birth Of A Child",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Date",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Job Interview",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a 'Thinking man's game'", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Chess",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Trivial Pursuit",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Jeopardy",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Bridge",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Scrabble",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Risk",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a public place where you see parents disciplining their children", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Store",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Restaurant",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Church",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Park",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "School",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something office workers forget to turn off at the end of the day", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Lights",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Typewriter",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Copy Machine",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Coffee Maker",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Computer",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Calculator",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation in which people make headlines", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Politics",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Show Business",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Athletics",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Firefighter",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Police",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Lawyer",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you would see around a fireplace", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Firewood",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Fireplace Tools",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Fire Screen",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Matches",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Andirons",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Mantel",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a man on his own asks his mother to do around the house", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Laundry",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Cook",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Clean",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Iron",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Decorate",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Sew",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a musical instrument played at weddings", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Organ",
"votes": 64
},
{"name": "Piano",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Violin",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Harp",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Guitar",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Flute",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you do on your hands & knees", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Scrub Floors",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "Crawl",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Look",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Pray",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Exercise",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Garden",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something kids love to ride on", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Horse",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Bicycle",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Merry Go Round",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Roller Coaster",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Train",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something most people do at the same time every day of their lives", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Eat",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Go To Bed",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Work",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Wake Up",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Watch TV",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a food you couldn't pronounce when you were a small child", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Spaghetti",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Asparagus",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Banana",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Broccoli",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hamburger",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Tomato",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something about shopping malls that can be dangerous", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Parking Lot",
"votes": 46
},
{"name": "Escalator",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Crowd",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Wet Floor",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Fire",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that kids get dressed up for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Church",
"votes": 65
},
{"name": "Halloween",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Party",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Easter",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Picture",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a food that comes in instant form", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Potatoes",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Oatmeal",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Coffee",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Pudding",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Soup",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Rice",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a specific activity for which people buy special sneakers", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Jogging",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Basketball",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Tennis",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Aerobics",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Walking",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something little kids hate to do", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Go To Bed",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Take A Bath",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Brush Teeth",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Clean Room",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Eat Vegetables",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Pick Up Toys",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a magazine that usually has a celebrity's face on the cover", 
"Answers": [{"name": "People",
"votes": 62
},
{"name": "TV Guide",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Time",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "National Enquirer",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Life",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that decays", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Teeth",
"votes": 81
},
{"name": "Fruit",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Leaves",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Wood",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Body",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Meat",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you associate with Australia", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Kangaroos",
"votes": 71
},
{"name": "Koala Bear",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Crocodile Dundee",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Sheep",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Outback",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What do many young husbands promise they'll get their wives 'Someday'",
"Answers": [{"name": "House",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Jewelry",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you use that comes with three or more settings", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Blender",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Bicycle",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Washer",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Fan",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hair Dryer",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Give me the name of any gauge on your car's dashboard", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Fuel",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "Speedometer",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Odometer",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Oil",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Temperature",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Tachometer",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a food that's hard to keep on your fork", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Peas",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Spaghetti",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Rice",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Soup",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Corn",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that changes from green to yellow", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Leaves",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Traffic Light",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Banana",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Grass",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Apple",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Squash",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation parents want their daughters to have", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Nurse",
"votes": 39
},
{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Physician",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Attorney",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Model",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Secretary",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you eat only when you're in the mood", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ice Cream",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Candy",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Pizza",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Chinese Food",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Seafood",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something Shirley Temple is famous for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Curly Hair",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Acting",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Dancing",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Good Ship Lollipop",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Dimples",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Singing",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a specific luxury item that you own more than one of", 
"Answers": [{"name": "TV",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "VCR",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Ring",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Watch",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something children buy for the first day of school", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Pencil",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Lunch Box",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Crayons",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Notebook",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Paper",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you might find in a trunk in the attic", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Pictures",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Books",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Blankets",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Letters",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone famous whose last name is O'Neill or O'Neal", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ryan O'Neal",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Tip O'Neill",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Jennifer O'Neill",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Tatum O'Neal",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Eugene O'Neill",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Patrick O'Neill",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something parents tell their kids not to waste", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Food",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Time",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Water",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Electricity",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Toothpaste",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where you have a tough time trying to stay awake", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Church",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Movie",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Classroom",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "At A Speech",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Bed",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something for which you might have to take a physical exam", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Job",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Insurance Policy",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Army",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Sport",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "School",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Camp",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name the household appliance that people need most", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Refrigerator",
"votes": 62
},
{"name": "Stove",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Washer",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Microwave",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Toaster",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you'd find inside a haunted house", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ghost",
"votes": 39
},
{"name": "Cobweb",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Skeleton",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Creaky Staircase",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Witches",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that superstitious people think brings good luck", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Rabbit's Foot",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Four Leaf Clover",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Horseshoe",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Knock On Wood",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Lucky Penny",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that comes in a spray can", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hair Spray",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Paint",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Deodorant",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Bug Spray",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Furniture Polish",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you steam", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Vegetables",
"votes": 66
},
{"name": "Clams",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Rice",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Shrimp",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people save as mementos of their vacations", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Photographs",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Postcards",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Match Books",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Ashtrays",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Ticket Stubs",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Towels",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you have to do for a successful vegetable garden", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Water It",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Weed It",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Fertilize It",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Till The Soil",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Mulch",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of store where people do more looking than buying", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Jewelry Store",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Furniture Store",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Car Dealer",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Clothing Store",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Antique Store",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something of yours that you wouldn't want anyone to borrow", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Underwear",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Toothbrush",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Comb",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that looks better on young girls than older women", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Miniskirt",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Bathing Suit",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Ponytail",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Ribbon",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Shorts",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Makeup",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone you deal with all year to whom you give a gift at Christmas", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Boss",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Postman",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Paper Boy",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Hairdresser",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Friend",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people fall out of", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Love",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Bed",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Trees",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Airplane",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Hammock",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you put on a baby", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Diapers",
"votes": 81
},
{"name": "Baby Powder",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Baby Lotion",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Bib",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Socks",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you hate to see young girls wearing", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Makeup",
"votes": 75
},
{"name": "Miniskirts",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Short Shorts",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Tacky Jewelry",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Tight Clothes",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a job that requires working on a rooftop", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Roofing",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Chimney Sweep",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Antenna",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Fixing Leaks",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Cleaning Gutters",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Construction",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something specific that women eat when they're mad", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Candy",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "Chips",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Ice Cream",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Cookies",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Cake",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that has a kid's name on it, so he won't lose it at school", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Coat",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Lunch Box",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Mittens",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Boot",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Book Bag",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something specific that you file", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Income Tax Papers",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Nails",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Bills",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Receipts",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Insurance Papers",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Letters",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of roller", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hair Roller",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Paint Roller",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Roller Skate",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Roller Coaster",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Steamroller",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Rolling Pin",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides pets, name something you buy at a pet store", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Pet Food",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Toys",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Collar",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Cages",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Vitamins",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something from the old days that you had to crank to operate", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Telephone",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Phonograph",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Ice Cream Maker",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Water Pump",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something bought for a child's party", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Balloons",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Hats",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Cake",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Ice Cream",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Streamers",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Gifts",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place you go to find peace and quiet", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Outdoors",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Bathroom",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Library",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Bedroom",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Church",
"votes": 14
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that gives off heat", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Sun",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Stove",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Fire",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Radiation",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Heater",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Car Motor",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a product that comes with a fragrance added", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Soap",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Deodorant",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Shampoo",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Lotion",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Perfume",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Fabric Softener",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where you see many people reading", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Library",
"votes": 82
},
{"name": "Airplane",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Park",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "School",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Train",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that a person likes to do after a long trip", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Rest",
"votes": 65
},
{"name": "Shower",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Relax",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Stretch Legs",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Read Mail",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a child like to cuddle with", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Teddy Bear",
"votes": 73
},
{"name": "Blanket",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Doll",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Parent",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Grandparent",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that accidentally gets stuck on the roof", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Frisbee",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Ball",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Cat",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Kite",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Leaves",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Newspaper",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that is associated with southern belle", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Accent",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Fancy Dresses",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Hats",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Beauty",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Plantation",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a job that requires using the telephone a lot", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Sales",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Operator",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Receptionist",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Secretary",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Phone Polling",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something associated with a turtle", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Shell",
"votes": 60
},
{"name": "Being slow",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Hare",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Soup",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Water",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a police officer has on his or her belt", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Gun",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Handcuffs",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Night Stick",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Buckle",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Bullets",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you loved to sit on when you were a small child", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Someone's Lap",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Rocking Chair",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Floor",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Swing",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Rocking Horse",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you see little boys chasing", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Balls",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Girls",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Bogs",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Frogs",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Each Other",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Bugs",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a country in which there seems to be never ending violence", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Iraq",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Ireland",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Iran",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Israel",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Lebanon",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "United States",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation in which it would be a help to be a good listener", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Physician",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Clergy",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "School Counselor",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Attorney",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that's written on a college diploma", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Graduate's Name",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "College Name",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Date",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Type Of Degree",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Signatures",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "What does a fashion magazine tell you about a piece of clothing?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Designer",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Cost",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Fabric",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Where To Buy It",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Sizes Available",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Color",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Where's your favorite place to have a picnic?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Park",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Lake",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Beach",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Mountains",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Backyard",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Woods",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that always seems to run a little behind schedule", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Airplanes",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Buses",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Doctors",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Trains",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people do the minute they see a camera", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Smile",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Cover Face",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Pose",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Make Faces",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Fix Hair",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Look Away",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you'd expect to see on an exotic island", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Palm Trees",
"votes": 71
},
{"name": "Animal",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Beautiful Women",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Flower",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Dancers",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Sand",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a food that's good on a hot day", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ice Cream",
"votes": 52
},
{"name": "Melon",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Salad",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Sandwiches",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hot Dogs",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Past or present, name a famous horse from movies or TV", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Mr Ed",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Trigger",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Silver",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Black Beauty",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Flicka",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Scout",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something around the house that is a tipoff you have a pet", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Food Dish",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Litter",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Pet Hair",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Odor",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Pet Food",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Toys",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name one of the smells of summer", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Flowers",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Cut Grass",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Barbecue",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Rain",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Suntan Lotion",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "List a nicknamed outlaw besides wild Bill Hickok & pretty boy Floyd", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Billy The Kid",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Babyface Nelson",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Al Scarface Capone",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "The Sundance Kid",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Bugsy Malone",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you set", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Clock",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Table",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "VCR",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Timer",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something worn by a sheriff in western movies", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Badge",
"votes": 74
},
{"name": "Gun",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Cowboy Hat",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Vest",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Boots",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Spurs",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Tell me something colored blue", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Sky",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Jeans",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Eyes",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Water",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shirt",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a game considered to be played by the upper class", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Polo",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Chess",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Bridge",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Backgammon",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Golf",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Tennis",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something comfortable to wear that was once cheap but now isn't", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Shoes",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Blue Jeans",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "T Shirts",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Nightgown",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Perfume",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Sweater",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What activity would you think most people do after they retire?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Travel",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "Golf",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Fish",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Garden",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Read",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that always attracts a crowd", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Accident",
"votes": 39
},
{"name": "Fire",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Fight",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Parade",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Sale",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of engineer", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Electrical",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Railroad",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Civil",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Mechanical",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Chemical",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Aerospace",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people do on the floor", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Exercise",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Dance",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Site",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Watch TV",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Sleep",
"votes": 8
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that a doctor gives you", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Prescription",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Shots",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Bill",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Test",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Advice",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "What's the most important single word in marriage vows?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Love",
"votes": 65
},
{"name": "Honor",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "I Do",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Promise",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Cherish",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Obey",
"votes": 1
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a magician makes disappear", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Rabbit",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "People",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Bird",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Coin",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Rubber Ball",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that makes a high school kid conceited", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Sports Ability",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Good Looks",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Good Grades",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Popularity",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a popular machine you often must wait for at the health club", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Stationary Bike",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "Treadmill",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Rowing Machine",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Weights",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Stair Climber",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Soda Machine",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that goes great with cheese", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Crackers",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Wine",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Ham",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Apples",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Pasta",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you do on your knees", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Pray",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Clean floor",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Garden",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Beg",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Crawl",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a neighbor buys that becomes the talk of the neighborhood", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Swimming Pool",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Boat",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Hot Tub",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Motor Home",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a salesman carries with him", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Briefcase",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Samples",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Pen",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Business Cards",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Order Forms",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Calculator",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a summer vacation state", 
"Answers": [{"name": "California",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Florida",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Hawaii",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Colorado",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Oregon",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name the most worthwhile occupation", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Physician",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Clergyman",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Nurse",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Mother",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Police",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that some men still consider it unmanly to do", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cry",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Wash Dishes",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Housework",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Change Diapers",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Cook",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Wear Earring",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you see in every courtroom", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Judge",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Flag",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Gavel",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Jury Box",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Witness Stand",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Bailiff",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people place a drink on when they can't find a coaster", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Napkin",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Magazine",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Paper",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Ashtray",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Book",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a city known for its great restaurants", 
"Answers": [{"name": "New York",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "New Orleans",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Paris",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "San Francisco",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Chicago",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Los Angeles",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a job you can't believe they can't find anyone to do", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Garbage Collector",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Sewer",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Janitor",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Zoo Cleaner",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Mortician",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Window Washer",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a reason why a high school grad might put off going to college", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Money",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Job",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Tired Of School",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Wants To Travel",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Army",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that Frosty the Snowman had", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Corncob Pipe",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Old Top Hat",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Coal Eyes",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Button Nose",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Broomstick",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of item for which you'll never change brands", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Soap",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Coffee",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Cigarettes",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Toothpaste",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shampoo",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an instrument whose sound is made by blowing", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Trumpet",
"votes": 65
},
{"name": "Flute",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Saxophone",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Clarinet",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Tuba",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides mowing, what must you do to care for your lawn?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Water",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Fertilize",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Rake Leaves",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Edge",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Weed",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Tell me someone who should never take sides", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Judge",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Clergy",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Parents",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Sports Official",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a woman does to feel better after a bad haircut", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Go Shopping",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Re Style Hair",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Wear A Hat",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Cry",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Eat Sweets",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Wear A Wig",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Past or present, name a famous female comedy star", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Lucille Ball",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Carol Burnett",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Roseanne Arnold",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Gilda Radner",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Joan Rivers",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Phyllis Diller",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation in which you wear gloves", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Physician",
"votes": 44
},
{"name": "Dentist",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Gardener",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Boxer",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Welder",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Who does a married woman turn to when she and her husband fight?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Friend",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Mother",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Self",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Sister",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Daughter",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you do at a mirror", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Comb Hair",
"votes": 39
},
{"name": "Apply Makeup",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Shave",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Look",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Brush Teeth",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Smile",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that might cost a million dollars", 
"Answers": [{"name": "House",
"votes": 64
},
{"name": "Yacht",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Airplane",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Painting",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Business",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Jewelry",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you can now buy unsalted", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Peanuts",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Crackers",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Potato Chips",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Canned Vegetables",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Pretzels",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of tube", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Inner Tube",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Test Tube",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Toothpaste",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "TV Picture",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Fallopian",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something men replace when they achieve fame & fortune", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Wife",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "House",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name the one thing you've bought that's made you the happiest", 
"Answers": [{"name": "House",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Pet",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "VCR",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Wedding Ring",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a bad habit that usually makes a person a bad roommate", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Messy",
"votes": 74
},
{"name": "Smoking",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Snoring",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Too Neat",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Body Odor",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Lazy",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you'd see at a seance", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Crystal Ball",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Candles",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Table",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Medium",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Holding Hands",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a reason why people can't fall asleep", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Worries",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Caffeine",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Insomnia",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Loud Noises",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Hot Weather",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you can use as collateral for a loan", 
"Answers": [{"name": "House",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Stocks",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Jewelry",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you see at a bus stop", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bench",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "People",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Bus Stop Sign",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Bus",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Schedule",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where you talk to someone through a glass window", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bank",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Jail",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Movie",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Doctor's Office",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Gas Station",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a famous Charlie", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Charlie Chaplin",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Charlie Brown",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Charlie Chan",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Charlie McCarthy",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Charlie The Tuna",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a job that a person might hold at a summer camp", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Counselor",
"votes": 73
},
{"name": "Lifeguard",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Director",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Cook",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Swimming Teacher",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a decision people won't make until they 'Sleep on it'", 
"Answers": [{"name": "New Car",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "New Home",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Getting Married",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Changing Jobs",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Surgery",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something an obnoxious driver does", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Tailgates",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Blows Horn",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Cuts People Off",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Gestures",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Drives Slow",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hogs Road",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people take for granted until they get older", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Health",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Eyesight",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Parent",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Youth",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a girl wears to show off her figure", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bikini",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Tight Sweater",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Tight Jeans",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Miniskirt",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Bra",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Tank Top",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that is usually done when a person gets a makeover", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hair Cut",
"votes": 66
},
{"name": "New Nose",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Facial",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Makeup",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Facelift",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Manicure",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that gets passed around the office", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Gossip",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Memos",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Jokes",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Cold",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Cards",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a phrase that has the word 'United' in it", 
"Answers": [{"name": "United States",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "United We Stand",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "United In Marriage",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "United Nations",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "United Way",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "United Airlines",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Real of fictional, name a famous prince", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Charles",
"votes": 56
},
{"name": "Charming",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Valiant",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Albert",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Philip",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something only women used to do to their hair that men do now too", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Perm",
"votes": 44
},
{"name": "Hair Spray",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Color",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Blow Dry",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Mousse",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Grow Long",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something with a hole in the middle", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Donut",
"votes": 84
},
{"name": "Tire",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Bagel",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Lifesaver",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Record",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Ring",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of product that uses scantily clad men in its ads", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Underwear",
"votes": 64
},
{"name": "Swim Suits",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Cologne",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Deodorant",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shaving Cream",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an appropriate occupation for a 'Good Samaritan'", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Nurse",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Clergyman",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Social Worker",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Police",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Physician",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Firefighter",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a subject of the posters that children hang on their walls", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Rock Stars",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Animals",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Sports",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Disney Characters",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "TV Stars",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Sesame St Characters",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "What one thing provides the best protection for your home?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Burglar Alarm",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Dog",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Locks",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Insurance",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Smoke Alarm",
"votes": 9
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you would take with you for an extra long car trip", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Food",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Pillow",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Book",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Cooler",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Map",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you're sure to see in every horror movie", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Blood",
"votes": 75
},
{"name": "Monster",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Screaming People",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Death",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Thunderstorm",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people want their food to be low in", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Fat",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Calories",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Cholesterol",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Salt",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Sugar",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation kids think is heroic", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Firefighter",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Police Officer",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Astronaut",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Pilot",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Pro Athlete",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Race Car Driver",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone you tip", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Waiter",
"votes": 83
},
{"name": "Hairdresser",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Bag Handler",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Bellhop",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Parking Attendant",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people cut their fingers on", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Knife",
"votes": 44
},
{"name": "Paper",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Glass",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Grater",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Razor",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people 'Pull up'", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Pants",
"votes": 46
},
{"name": "Socks",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Weeds",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Pantyhose",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shades",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Covers",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a food that leaves you with a couple of days of leftovers", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Turkey",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Pasta",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Roast Beef",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Meat Loaf",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Chili",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Soup",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Tell me an animal you'd recognize from a picture of its ears", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Elephant",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Rabbit",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Dog",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Donkey",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Cat",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Horse",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides restaurants, name a place where you eat a lot of junk food", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Movies",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Sporting Event",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Party",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Carnival",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Bowling Alley",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people complain to their landlord about", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Plumbing",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Heat",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Rent",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Noise",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Roof",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Neighbors",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name the first flower that pops up each spring", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Crocus",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Tulip",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Daffodil",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Daisy",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Buttercup",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Dandelion",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a way clams are served", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Steamed",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Fried",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "On The Half Shell",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Chowder",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Broiled",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something most people try to keep secret about themselves", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Age",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Finances",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Love Life",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Weight",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Baby",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something Jane Fonda is famous for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Exercise",
"votes": 62
},
{"name": "Protests",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Acting",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Her Father",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Politics",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that London is famous for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Big Ben",
"votes": 44
},
{"name": "Fog",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "London Bridge",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Royal Family",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Buckingham Palace",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Changing Of The Guard",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "If you had four extra hours a day, what would you do with them?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Sleep",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Read",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Family",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Rest",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Exercise",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Golf",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occasion for which you might be tempted to rent a fancy car", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Prom",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Reunion",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Anniversary",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Vacation",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people start but never finish", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Diet",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Books",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Puzzles",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Repairs",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Clean House",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Letter",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an afternoon activity organized by ladies' clubs", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Card Game",
"votes": 44
},
{"name": "Luncheon",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Bake Sale",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Fashion Show",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Bazaar",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Garden Club",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that uses batteries", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Flashlight",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Radio",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Toys",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Clock",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides swimming, name something people do in a bathing suit", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Sunbathe",
"votes": 85
},
{"name": "Exercise",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hot Tub",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Model",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Water Ski",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people spray on themselves", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Perfume",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Deodorant",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Insect Repellent",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Hair Spray",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Water",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something used by both armies & police departments", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Guns",
"votes": 81
},
{"name": "Tear Gas",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Two Way Road",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Uniforms",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Helicopter",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people buy that comes in 'Stick' form", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Gun",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Deodorant",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Butter",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Lipstick",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Glue",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an instrument in a real 'Hillbilly' band", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Banjo",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Fiddle",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Washboard",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Jug",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Guitar",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name one of the highlights of your teenage years", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Prom",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Graduation",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Dating",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Driving",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Kiss",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a country that was involved in World War II", 
"Answers": [{"name": "USA",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Germany",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Japan",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "England",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "France",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you'd do at dinner at home you wouldn't do in a restaurant", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Burp",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Eat With Fingers",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Elbows On Table",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Drink From Bowl",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Pick Teeth",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a complaint people have about the beach", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Too Crowded",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Litter",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Hate Sand",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Animals",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Too Many Kids",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What one thing would you buy if you won a million dollars?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "New House",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "New Car",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Boat",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Securities",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Housekeeper",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Jacuzzi",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people worry about losing", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Job",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Keys",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Wallet",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a child's pet that you don't pet", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Fish",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Snake",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Turtle",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Frog",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Spider",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that prevents you from getting to bed early", 
"Answers": [{"name": "TV",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Phone",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Children",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Guest",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Work",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something most people have more of than they need", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Shoes",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Fat",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Bills",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Food",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Time",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that new mothers have to carry wherever they go", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Diaper Bag",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Diapers",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Baby",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Formula",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Stroller",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides the US, name a country you think has lots of billionaires", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Japan",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Saudi Arabia",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "France",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "England",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Switzerland",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Italy",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something children need before they can move away from home", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Job",
"votes": 39
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Education",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place of business where armored trucks make pickups", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bank",
"votes": 64
},
{"name": "Grocery",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Department Store",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Casino",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Restaurant",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a memento a woman saves from her first love", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Letters",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Flowers",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Ring",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Pictures",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Gift",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Cards",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a wife asks her husband to pick up on the way home", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Milk",
"votes": 65
},
{"name": "Bread",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Dinner",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Dry Cleaning",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Children",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Tell me something that people save from their weddings", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cake",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "Dress",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Flowers",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Pictures",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Garter",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Napkins",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a good place for pickpockets to work", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Airport",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Amusement Park",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Subway",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Sports Event",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Shopping Mall",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Concert",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of chip", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Potato",
"votes": 56
},
{"name": "Chocolate",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Poker",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Computer",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Corn",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that goes great with steak", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Potatoes",
"votes": 73
},
{"name": "Salad",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Mushrooms",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Onions",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Beans",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a person who expects you to pay attention to him or her", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Children",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Boss",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Parents",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you hate to wait for while it warms up", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Curling Iron",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Coffee",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Oven",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Water",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you ask a dentist to recommend", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Toothpaste",
"votes": 67
},
{"name": "Toothbrush",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Orthodontist",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Mouthwash",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Pain Reliever",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you do to your hair that could damage it", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bleach",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Perm",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Blow Day",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Tease",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Too Much Sun",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that children love to ride on", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bike",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Horse",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Merry Go Round",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Back",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Roller Coaster",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a pet that draws crowds to pet store windows", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Puppy",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Kitten",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Monkey",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Snake",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Birds",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a part of your car once made of metal, now made of plastic", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bumpers",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "Dash",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Fenders",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Grill",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Steering Wheel",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Hubcaps",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something made of lace", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Tablecloth",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Wedding Dress",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Underwear",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Doily",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Nightgown",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Collar",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that must operate on a strict time schedule", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Airline",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Train",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "School",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Bus",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Work",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something parents save from a first baby to use for a second", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Crib",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Blanket",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Shoes",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "High Chair",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Play Pen",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What board game do you play best?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Monopoly",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Scrabble",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Checkers",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Trivial Pursuit",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Pictionary",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Backgammon",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you ought to have before you start a family", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Money",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Job",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "House",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Insurance",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people pound", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Nails",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Meat",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Fist",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Pavement",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Desk",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Dough",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a fairy tale that is also a love story", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cinderella",
"votes": 56
},
{"name": "Sleeping Beauty",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Snow White",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Beauty And The Beast",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Rapunzel",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a country where you think the U.S. has spies", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Russia",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Iraq",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Saudi Arabia",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Germany",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Iran",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Cuba",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of place that always has uncomfortable furniture", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Doctor's Office",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "Church",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Airport",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "School",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Station",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hospital",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a sign no one seems to obey", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Speed Limit",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Yield",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Stop",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "No Smoking",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Don't Walk",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Keep Off The Grass",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a strange place people who don't trust banks keep money", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Under Mattress",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Buried",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Cookie Jar",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Freezer",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Sock",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Which one thing would you want to inherit from wealthy relatives?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Money",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "House",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Jewelry",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Antiques",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Business",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Stocks",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that a man first notices about a woman", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Figure",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Legs",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Eyes",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Face",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Smile",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "After a child moves away, what do his parents use his room for?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Guest Room",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Den",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Storage",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Sewing Room",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Study",
"votes": 9
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people cheat on", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Income Tax",
"votes": 67
},
{"name": "Test",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Diet",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Cards",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of food that people put in crepes", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Fruit",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Cheese",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Chicken",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Eggs",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Seafood",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Meat",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a game families play around the kitchen table", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Monopoly",
"votes": 46
},
{"name": "Cards",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Scrabble",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Yahtzee",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Trivial Pursuit",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Tell me a type of place that has uniformed guards", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bank",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Jail",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Military Base",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Buckingham Palace",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Embassy",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Museum",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "What do the colors red & white make you think of?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "American Flag",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Candy Cane",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Valentine",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Red Cross",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "School Colors",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Barber Pole",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a likely place to find a missing sock", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bed",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Dryer",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Washing Machine",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Drawer",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Laundry",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Pant Leg",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a decision the whole family makes together", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Vacation",
"votes": 62
},
{"name": "Moving",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Eat",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Pet",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a president, past or present, who was idolized by many people", 
"Answers": [{"name": "John F. Kennedy",
"votes": 58
}
]},
{"Question": "Franklin D. Roosevelt.15", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Abraham Lincoln",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Ronald Reagan",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "George Washington",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Dwight Eisenhower",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides eating, name something you do while having breakfast", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Read",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Watch TV",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Listen To Radio",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Crossword",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Talk",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone you'd see hanging around outside a sports stadium", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ticket Scalper",
"votes": 56
},
{"name": "Vendor",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Police",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Children",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Fans",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Reporters",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "What's the most important quality an employee can have?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Honesty",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Loyalty",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Dependable",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Hard Working",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Prompt",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something kids trade school lunch sandwiches for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Dessert",
"votes": 78
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Other Sandwich",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Fruit",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Toys",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "On a daily basis, what do you worry about most?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Money",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Family",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Health",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Work",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Weight",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you always carry in your car but rarely use", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Flashlight",
"votes": 39
},
{"name": "Spare Tire",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Jack",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Jumper Cables",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Map",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Umbrella",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something your conscience tells you not to do", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Lie",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Steal",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Overeat",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Cheat",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Eat Sweets",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Gossip",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a well known Cape", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cape Cod",
"votes": 70
},
{"name": "Cape Canaveral",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Cape Of Good Hope",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Cape Horn",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Cape Hatteras",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a common interest that brings groups of adults together", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Children",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Sports",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Church",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Card Games",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Parties",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation whose people deal with emergencies", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Paramedic",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Firefighter",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Physician",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Nurse",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Police",
"votes": 13
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that knocks", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "People",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Woodpecker",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Door Knocker",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Knees",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Opportunity",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an job in which you're expected to know your way around a city", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Taxi",
"votes": 73
},
{"name": "Police",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Tour Guide",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Bus Driver",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Mail Carrier",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you have for breakfast when you're in a hurry", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Toast",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Cereal",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Donut",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Coffee",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Juice",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a famous cartoon bird", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Tweety Pie",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Woody Woodpecker",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Big Bird",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Road Runner",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Donald Duck",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Woodstock",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a job that makes so much noise it wakes you up in the morning", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Garbage Collection",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Construction",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Jackhammer Operator",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Lawn Mowing",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Vacuuming",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone to whom kids tell 'Little white lies'", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Parents",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Friends",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Grandparents",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Santa Claus",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something for which you're saving money", 
"Answers": [{"name": "New Car",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "New Home",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Vacation",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Retirement",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "College",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you might rent while you're on vacation", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 44
},
{"name": "Cabin",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Hotel Room",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Boat",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Motor Home",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you can do while talking on the phone", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cook",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Wash Dishes",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Write",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Watch TV",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Do Nails",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Eat",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides diapers, name something that new moms carry in diaper bags", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bottle",
"votes": 65
},
{"name": "Baby Wipes",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Powder",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Pacifier",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of place where young lovers kiss for the first time", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Movies",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Front Door",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Dance",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Park",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where you've used a lot of excuses", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Work",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "School",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Bedroom",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Court",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Doctor's Office",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a family does together", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Eat",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Vacation",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Church",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Picnic",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Watch TV",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Argue",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of seafood used in soup", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Clam",
"votes": 67
},
{"name": "Shrimp",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Oyster",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Crab",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Lobster",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of agent", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Government Agent",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Insurance Agent",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Real Estate Agent",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Talent Agent",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Travel Agent",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an event that celebrities use to get their pictures in the papers", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Award Ceremony",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Charity",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Show Premier",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Party",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something parents want to know about a daughter's boyfriend", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Age",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Job",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Family",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Where He Lives",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Name",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you keep handy near your front door", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Umbrella",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Coats",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Keys",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Doormat",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Light Switch",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name any member of Britain's royal family", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Prince Charles",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Princess Diane",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Queen Elizabeth",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Sarah Ferguson",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Prince Andrew",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an excuse that people use to get out of jury duty", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Illness",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Work",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Care For Child",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Know About Case",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Know People",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Out Of Town",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something parents take movies of their baby doing", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Walking",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Taking A Bath",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Crawling",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Eating",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Playing",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Birthday",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a bad occupation for a person who's afraid of heights", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Window Washer",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Construction",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Pilot",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Painter",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Roofer",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Flight Attendant",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a rule that should be enforced on the beach", 
"Answers": [{"name": "No Grass",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "No Litter",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "No Alcohol",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "No Animals",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "No Nudity",
"votes": 10
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a holiday that can be lots of fun or a lot of aggravation", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Christmas",
"votes": 78
},
{"name": "Halloween",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Thanksgiving",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Fourth Of July",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "New Year's Eve",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that club members vote on", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Officers",
"votes": 46
},
{"name": "Members",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Rules",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Dues",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a person might have but won't tell you it's fake", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Jewelry",
"votes": 56
},
{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Teeth",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Watch",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Fur Coat",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Painting",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that everybody usually does every day", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Eat",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Brush Teeth",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Bathe",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Get Up",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Work",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a gift that will soothe a wife's ruffled feathers", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Flowers",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Jewelry",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Candy",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Night Out",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Card",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Give me another word for an 'Informer'", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Snitch",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Spy",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Stool Pigeon",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Squealer",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Rat",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Tattletale",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a specific food that comes with different toppings", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ice Cream",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Pizza",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Cake",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Potato",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Salad",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Pie",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you wash every day", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Dishes",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Face",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Hands",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an appliance that lasts for years", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Refrigerator",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Stove",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Washer",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Mixer",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Toaster",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that a couple has a favorite one of", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Song",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "Restaurant",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Picture",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Vacation Spot",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "TV Show",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a way you can tell someone is nervous", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Biting Nails",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Shaking",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Fidgeting",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Sweating",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Tapping Fingers",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Stuttering",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people serve at Thanksgiving instead of Turkey", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ham",
"votes": 80
},
{"name": "Goose",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Roast Beef",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Chicken",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Duck",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that might have powdered sugar on it", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Donut",
"votes": 67
},
{"name": "French Toast",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Cookie",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Cake",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Brownies",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that can make a house shake", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Earthquake",
"votes": 75
},
{"name": "Truck Passing",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Hurricane",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Explosion",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Thunder",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Sonic Boom",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you bring indoors when it's very windy outside", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Patio Furniture",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Plants",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Pets",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Flag",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a dance associated with another country", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Polka",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Tango",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Mexican Hat Dance",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Irish Jig",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Can Can",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you wish you could stop doing right now", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Smoking",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Eating",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Working",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Biting Nails",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Worrying",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a handy little device other than rubber bands", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Paper Clips",
"votes": 72
},
{"name": "Stapler",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Safety Pin",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Scissors",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Tape",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "If you were fundamentally dishonest, what occupation would you choose?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Sales",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Politics",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Banking",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Attorney",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Thief",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Tell me something annoying that cats do", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Scratch",
"votes": 60
},
{"name": "Rub Against You",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Meow",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Climb",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shed",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a man thinks makes him look unsexy", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Fat",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Sloppy",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Long Hair",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Dirty",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Beard",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Bald",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a household chore that needs to be done again right away", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Dishes",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Dusting",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Floors",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Laundry",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Trash Removal",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a word used to describe people who are overweight, besides big", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Fat",
"votes": 52
},
{"name": "Obese",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Chubby",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Heavy",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Plump",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something besides collars, that some dresses have & some don't", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Belts",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Sleeves",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Buttons",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Zipper",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Pockets",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Waistbands",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "When you're having problems with your spouse, who do you tell?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Friend",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Sibling",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Parent",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Nobody",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that's hidden that kids try to find", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Presents",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Easter Eggs",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Candy",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Cookies",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What one thing makes your house a home?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Love",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Family",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Pet",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Pictures",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a way little kids are punished", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Spanking",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Sent To Room",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "No TV",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Grounding",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "No Dinner",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "No Allowance",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something specific you might hide", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Money",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Jewelry",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Diary",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Gifts",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Keys",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Real or fictional, name a famous boxer", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Muhammad Ali",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Joe Louis",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Mike Tyson",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Rocky Balboa",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Sugar Ray Leonard",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Joe Frazier",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you can find on the table at a restaurant", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Salt & Pepper",
"votes": 72
},
{"name": "Napkins",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Ketchup",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Sugar",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Flowers",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Menu",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a white animal", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Polar Bear",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Rabbit",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Cat",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Horse",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Seal",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a special 'Perk' that executives often enjoy", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Company Car",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Travel",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Executive Restroom",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Expense Account",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Limo Service",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Parking Space",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something boy scouts are famous for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Good Deeds",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Camping",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Tying Knots",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Being Prepared",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Scout's Honor",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people tune", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Piano",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Guitar",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Radio",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Violin",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something the family takes turns using", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bathroom",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Hair Dryer",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Phone",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something important that you keep in your glove compartment", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Registration",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Flashlight",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Insurance Card",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Map",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "First Aid Kit",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people do to emphasize a point they're making", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Raise Voice",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Point",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Wave Hands",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Pound Desk",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Curse",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation in which you get your picture taken a lot", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Model",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Actor",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Politician",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Athlete",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "TV Reporter",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a specific kind of whale", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Killer Whale",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Sperm Whale",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Blue Whale",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Humpback Whale",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Gray Whale",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Beluga Whale",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where you often see a band performing", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Parade",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Nightclub",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Sporting Event",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Park",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Fair",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something inside your car that you frequently touch with your hands", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Steering Wheel",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Radio",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Turn Signal",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Rearview Mirror",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shift",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people donate to their church", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Money",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Time",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Food",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone you might allow to think is smarter than you are", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Boss",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Parent",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Kids",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Police",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you'd order 'Well done' in a restaurant", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Steak",
"votes": 79
},
{"name": "Hamburger",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Eggs",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Fish",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Pork",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Roast Beef",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Tell something you do to keep alert when you're working late", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Drink Coffee",
"votes": 74
},
{"name": "Listen To Music",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Drink Soda",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Chew Gum",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Eat",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Sing",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What do you put on a peanut butter sandwich besides peanut butter?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Jelly",
"votes": 74
},
{"name": "Banana",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Butter",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Marshmallow Spread",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Pickles",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What do you think most of the water mankind uses is for?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bathing",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Flushing Toilets",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Drinking",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Laundry",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Irrigation",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a university famous only for its great football team", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Notre Dame",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "UCLA",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Nebraska",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "USC",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Alabama",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Oklahoma",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone who compliments you almost every day", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Children",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Parent",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Friend",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Boss",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation that benefits society but doesn't get paid well", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Police",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Nurse",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Social Worker",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Firefighter",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people put in a casserole", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Noodles",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Tuna",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Meat",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Cheese",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Rice",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Potatoes",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a song made famous by Elvis Presley", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hound Dog",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Love Me Tender",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Blue Suede Shoes",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Jailhouse Rock",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Don't Be Cruel",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Heartbreak Hotel",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Past or present, real or fictional, name a famous robin", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Robin Hood",
"votes": 80
},
{"name": "Robin Williams",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Robin Red Breast",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Christopher Robin",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Batman & Robin",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name the one household appliance a woman would hate to be without", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Microwave",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Refrigerator",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Washing Machine",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Dishwasher",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Coffee Maker",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Stove",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that comes in a monthly club other than books", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Record",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Dessert",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Flower",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Video",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Fruit",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a state where you might still see cowboys", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Texas",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Montana",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Wyoming",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Arizona",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Colorado",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Oklahoma",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a hobby that men might devote more time to than to their families", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Golf",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Fishing",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Cars",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Hunting",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Computers",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people take from restaurants as souvenirs", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ashtrays",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Matches",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Salt & Pepper",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Napkins",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Place Mat",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Silverware",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Where do you look around the house, hoping to find cash?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Drawers",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Pockets",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Couch",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Piggy Bank",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Purse",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Cookie Jar",
"votes": 10
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something on a peanut butter sandwich besides peanut butter", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Jelly",
"votes": 74
},
{"name": "Banana",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Butter",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Marshmallow",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Pickles",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that husbands & wives fight over the use of", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Bathroom",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Telephone",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a sport with expensive equipment", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Skiing",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Golf",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Auto Racing",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Football",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Hockey",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Scuba",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a new miss America does the moment she's crowned", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cries",
"votes": 76
},
{"name": "Walks Runway",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Wears Crown",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Smiles",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Waves",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name your favorite fried food", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Potatoes",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Chicken",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Fish",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Shrimp",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hamburger",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Onion Rings",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place you'd expect to see tents", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Campground",
"votes": 69
},
{"name": "Circus",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Mountains",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "National Park",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Army",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone that people have to hire if they decide to build a house", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Contractor",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Carpenter",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Architect",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Electrician",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Plumber",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone connected with Jackie Onassis", 
"Answers": [{"name": "John F. Kennedy",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "John Kennedy Jr",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Caroline",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Aristotle Onassis",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Ted Kennedy",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that people just can't make themselves throw away", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Pictures",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Old Love Letters",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Books",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Shoes",
"votes": 8
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you might hear that would make you call the police", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Gunshot",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Scream",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Breaking Glass",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Car Crash",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Door",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Fight",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that might get overloaded", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Circuit",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Truck",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Washer",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Computer",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Telephone Line",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name two performers who made movies together as a team", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Martin & Lewis",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Hope & Crosby",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Redford & Newman",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Abbott & Costello",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Hepburn & Tracy",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Laurel & Hardy",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a little kid might try to sell to make money", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Lemonade",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Toys",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Bicycle",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Baseball Cards",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Sibling",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Newspaper",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "What living creature frightens women most?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Snake",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Spider",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Mouse",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Dog",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Bug",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shark",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something women do for hours on end", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Talk",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Keep House",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Watch TV",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Primp",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Shop",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Cook",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something parents learn to do for a new baby", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Change Diapers",
"votes": 65
},
{"name": "Feed",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Bathe",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Burp",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Make Formula",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that drives cats crazy", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Catnip",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Dogs",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Mice",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Yarn",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Bath",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Birds",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a food that's supposed to be good for you, but tastes awful", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Spinach",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Liver",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Yogurt",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Tofu",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Brussels Sprouts",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Bran",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of scope", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Telescope",
"votes": 66
},
{"name": "Microscope",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Rifle Scope",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Periscope",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Scope Mouthwash",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something padded", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bra",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Cell",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Chair",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Football Uniform",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Mattress",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Dashboard",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that makes a man look distinguished", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Gray Hair",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Moustache",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Beard",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Pipe",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that comes in pairs", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Shoes",
"votes": 69
},
{"name": "Socks",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Pants",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Salt & Pepper",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Twins",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a contestant in a beauty pageant is judged on", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Talent",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Poise",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Figure",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Good Looks",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Personality",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Intelligence",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a couple should agree on before they get married", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Children",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Finances",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Religion",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Wedding Details",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Where To Live",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Who's The Boss",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a piece of information a brochure gives you about a hotel", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Rates",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Swimming Pool",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Location",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Activities",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Dining",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you might find on a front porch", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Glider",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "Chair",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Doormat",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Newspaper",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Mailbox",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Plant",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "What might people be talking about if you overhear the word 'Moose'",
"Answers": [{"name": "Hunting",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Fat Person",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Dessert",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Moose Lodge",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Animals",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something your mother insisted you wear in the winter", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hat",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Coat",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Gloves",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Boots",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Scarf",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a young woman puts in her hope chest", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bed",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "China",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Lingerie",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Silverware",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Quilts",
"votes": 8
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a type of food you look over carefully before buying", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Meat",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Vegetables",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Fruit",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Fish",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Eggs",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you eat that sticks between your teeth", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 56
},
{"name": "Meat",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Caramel",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Peanut Butter",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Seeds",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something women talk about at work that drives men crazy", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Husband",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Kids",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Soap Opera",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Diet",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you find under the seat in a movie theater", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Gum",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Drink",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Candy",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shoes",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a president who used his middle initial", 
"Answers": [{"name": "John F. Kennedy",
"votes": 55
}
]},
{"Question": "Franklin D. Roosevelt.18", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Harry S Truman",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Dwight D. Eisenhower",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Lyndon B. Johnson",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where it bothers you most if people smoke", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Restaurant",
"votes": 58
},
{"name": "Bathroom",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Airplane",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Elevator",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Office",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something close friends often share with each other", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Secrets",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Problems",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Feelings",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Dream",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Food",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something pirates are famous for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Robbery",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Treasure",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Eye Patch",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Walking Plank",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Skull & Crossbones",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Wooden Leg",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you do with leftover food", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Freeze",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Reheat",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Throw It Out",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Feed Pet",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Make Casseroles",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Make Soup",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of pool other than a whirlpool", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Swimming Pool",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "Cesspool",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Carpool",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Wading Pool",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Pool Table",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you always see on the news", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Weather",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Crime",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Sports",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Auto Accidents",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Middle East",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Newscaster",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Which would country do you think is last alphabetically?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Zimbabwe",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Zambia",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Zaire",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Yugoslavia",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "United States",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Venezuela",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that changes color over a period of time", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Leaves",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Chameleon",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Clothing",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Flowers",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Grass",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something newlyweds save for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Home",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Baby",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Vacation",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What makes the news when it happens in the British Royal Family?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "New Baby",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Fight",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Travel",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Affair",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you eat by the handful", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Nuts",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Chips",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Candy",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Grapes",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occasion for which people gather in a church", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 81
},
{"name": "Sunday Services",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Baptism",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Easter",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Christmas",
"votes": 1
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a business besides department stores that has many branches", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bank",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Grocery",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Restaurant",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Insurance",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Real Estate",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you'd find in a barn", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hay",
"votes": 62
},
{"name": "Cow",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Horse",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Corn",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Tractor",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people put on their lawns", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Fertilizer",
"votes": 56
},
{"name": "Water",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Grass Seed",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Bird Bath",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Lawn Furniture",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Weed Killer",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name on of a secretary's duties", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Typing",
"votes": 71
},
{"name": "Taking Dictation",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Answer Phones",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Coffee",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Filing",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you think is grossly overpriced", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Cars",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Real Estate",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Food",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Hospital",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Jewelry",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides holidays, name something that people celebrate", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Birthday",
"votes": 77
},
{"name": "Anniversary",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Promotion",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Graduation",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people tint or color", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 67
},
{"name": "Windows",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Eyeglasses",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Cake",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Easter Eggs",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people wax", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 64
},
{"name": "Floors",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Skis",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Moustache",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an excellent interviewer on TV", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Barbara Walters",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Oprah",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Phil Donahue",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Johnny Carson",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Larry King",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a state where you'd expect to find cactus", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Arizona",
"votes": 74
},
{"name": "Texas",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Nevada",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "New Mexico",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "California",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that has pockets", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Pants",
"votes": 65
},
{"name": "Coat",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Pool Table",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Apron",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Kangaroo",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Shirt",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that symbolizes love, like a 4 leaf clover symbolizes luck", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Heart",
"votes": 69
},
{"name": "Roses",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Cupid",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Dove",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Ring",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that magicians try to escape from", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Chest",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Chain",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Handcuffs",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Straitjacket",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Tank Of Water",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Safe",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you wish you could do when your boss yells at you", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Yell Back",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Quit",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Tell Him Off",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Hit Him",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Walk Out",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "If your job took you abroad, what would you miss about America?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Food",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Family",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Freedom",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Language",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Friends",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a sport whose women players are considered unfeminine", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Wrestling",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Body Building",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Basketball",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Football",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Roller Derby",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Tennis",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you'd find on a person's arm", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Watch",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Tattoo",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Hair",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Sleeve",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Bracelet",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Freckles",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that watches do these days besides tell you the time", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Show Day",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Ring Alarm",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Calculator",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Stopwatch",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Have TV",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a female star, past or present, known for her figure", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Marilyn Monroe",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Raquel Welch",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Betty Grable",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Dolly Parton",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Mae West",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Cher",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something your grandparents always forget about you", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Age",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Birthday",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Name",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Size",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Grade",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something in your house that creeks", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Floor",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Stairs",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Door",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Chair",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Roof",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you often buy five pounds of at a time", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Sugar",
"votes": 50
},
{"name": "Potatoes",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Flour",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Ground Beef",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Dog Food",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a story or rhyme featuring a character named Jack", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Jack & The Beanstalk",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Jack Sprat",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Jack & Jill",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Jack Be Nimble",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Little Jack Horner",
"votes": 6
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a pastime that used to be only for intellectuals & snobs", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Chess",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Polo",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Bridge",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Golf",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Tennis",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "What might bring a couple back from the brink of divorce?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Children",
"votes": 71
},
{"name": "Counseling",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Pregnancy",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Sickness",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a food that's sometimes glazed", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Donut",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Ham",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Cake",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Carrots",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Sweet Potatoes",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "If you're short of money, what's the one bill you're sure to pay?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Rent",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Electric",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Telephone",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Heat",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Auto Insurance",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Car Payment",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an appliance you can buy for under $50", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Toaster",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Can Opener",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Blender",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Coffee Maker",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Iron",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Electric Knife",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you usually forget to pack for an overnight trip", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Toothbrush",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Toothpaste",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Pajamas",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Shampoo",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Razor",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Robe",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something police use to help them track escaped criminals", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Dogs",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "Fingerprints",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Helicopters",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Photos",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Computer",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something your kids do when they fight that drives you crazy", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Yell",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Hit Each Other",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Call Names",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Tattle",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Cry",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Tease",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you see on a track", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Train",
"votes": 61
},
{"name": "Horse",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Runner",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Greyhound",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an animal a little boy would like but a little girl would not", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Snake",
"votes": 39
},
{"name": "Mouse",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Frog",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Lizard",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Rat",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Dog",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a public place where women sometimes put on their makeup", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Restaurant",
"votes": 41
},
{"name": "Restroom",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Work",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Store",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "What single thing frightens small children the most?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Dark",
"votes": 53
},
{"name": "Monster",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Strange Noises",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Thunder",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Strangers",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Dog",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an event so important you count the days until it happens", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 54
},
{"name": "Retirement",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Birth Of A Baby",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Birthday",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Graduation",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Vacation",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something made of foam rubber", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Pillows",
"votes": 64
},
{"name": "Mattress",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Carpet Pad",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Life Preserver",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Sponge",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a brand of refrigerator", 
"Answers": [{"name": "General Electric",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Frigidaire",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Whirlpool",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Westinghouse",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Amana",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Sears",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides Gilligan, name a survivor on Gilligan's Island", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Skipper",
"votes": 46
},
{"name": "Professor",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Mary Ann",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Ginger",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Mr Howell",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that every state has an 'Official' one of", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Flower",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Bird",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Flag",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Seal",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Motto",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Song",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you'd interrupt a phone conversation to turn off", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Stove",
"votes": 57
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Radio",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Running Water",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Dishwasher",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Iron",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something with stripes", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Flag",
"votes": 60
},
{"name": "Zebra",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Uniform",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Candy Cane",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Tiger",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a race car driver", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Mario Andretti",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Bobby or Al Unser",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Paul Newman",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Richard Petty",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "A.J. Foyt",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you eat that starts with the word 'Rice'", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Rice Pudding",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Rice Krispies",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Rice A Roni",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Rice Pilaf",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Rice Cakes",
"votes": 9
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people need for a sleigh ride", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Snow",
"votes": 48
},
{"name": "Horses",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Sleigh",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Warm Clothes",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Blankets",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What would be the worst thing you could be turned down for?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Job",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Loan",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Marriage",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Promotion",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Love",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a sport with rowdy spectators", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Football",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Hockey",
"votes": 28
},
{"name": "Soccer",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Wrestling",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Rodeo",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something found in a playground", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Swing",
"votes": 72
},
{"name": "Slide",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Merry Go Round",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Seesaw",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Sandbox",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something in life that often becomes over due", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Library Books",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Bills",
"votes": 30
},
{"name": "Baby",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Vacation",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Pay Raises",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something you're always in the middle of when the phone rings", 
"Answers": [{"name": "In Bathroom",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Watching TV",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Eating",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Housework",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Sleeping",
"votes": 7
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a teenage boy might borrow from his dad without asking", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Razor",
"votes": 33
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "After Shave",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Clothing",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Tools",
"votes": 8
}
]},
{"Question": "Give me the name of a male barnyard animal other than a rooster", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bull",
"votes": 75
},
{"name": "Ram",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Gander",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Steer",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Stallion",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Drake",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that, in almost every house, is too small", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bathroom",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Closet",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Kitchen",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Tub",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Refrigerator",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where a woman should go to meet a rich man", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Country Club",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Cruise",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Expensive Restaurant",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Resort",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Las Vegas",
"votes": 9
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides Christmas, name a holiday for which you make a lot of plans", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Thanksgiving",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Easter",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Fourth Of July",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "New Year's",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Halloween",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Without using a brand name, name a cereal that's been around for years", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Corn Flakes",
"votes": 71
},
{"name": "Oatmeal",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Raisin Bran",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Shredded Wheat",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Frosted Flakes",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a kind of party where you would be expected to bring a gift", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Birthday",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Shower",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Wedding",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Anniversary",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Housewarming",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Graduation",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where people leave an extra house key", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Under Doormat",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "In A Plant",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "With A Neighbor",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Under A Rock",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "In Mailbox",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Over Door",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something specific you would see in every old western movie", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Horse",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Saloon",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Gun",
"votes": 10
},
{"name": "Barroom Brawl",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Cowboy",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone you would tell if you were considering a divorce", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Friend ",
"votes": 36
},
{"name": "Parent",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Spouse",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Children",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Clergyman",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Sister",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something with an adhesive on it", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bandage",
"votes": 59
},
{"name": "Scotch Tape",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Postage Stamp",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Envelope",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Decal",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that can be popped", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 62
},
{"name": "Balloon",
"votes": 19
},
{"name": "Champagne",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Pimple",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Bubble",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone around whom you won't curse", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Parents",
"votes": 45
},
{"name": "Clergyman",
"votes": 43
},
{"name": "Children",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Grandmother",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Boss",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something mint flavored", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Gum",
"votes": 64
},
{"name": "Ice Cream",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Toothpaste",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Antacid",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Mouthwash",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Tea",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you often see on a fireplace mantel", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Pictures",
"votes": 47
},
{"name": "Clock",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Candles",
"votes": 11
},
{"name": "Trophy",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Vase",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Matches",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation which some consider to be unmasculine", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hairdresser",
"votes": 40
},
{"name": "Nurse",
"votes": 31
},
{"name": "Florist",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Secretary",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Dancer",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "What was your first job to earn money?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Baby Sitting",
"votes": 37
},
{"name": "Yard Work",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Paper Route",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Salesperson",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Waiter",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Fast Food Restaurant",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a couple getting married must learn to share", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Bathroom",
"votes": 42
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 26
},
{"name": "Bed",
"votes": 18
},
{"name": "Closet Space",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that you get people in the office to chip in for", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Gifts",
"votes": 64
},
{"name": "Flowers",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Party",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Coffee",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Baby Shower",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place where you might find a phone to use when yours is broken", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Neighbor",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Grocery",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Public Phone Booth",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Gas Station",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Work",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Restaurant",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Besides food, name something you might find in a picnic basket", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Napkins",
"votes": 32
},
{"name": "Plates",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Silverware",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Tablecloth",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Ants",
"votes": 8
}
]},
{"Question": "Past or present, name someone famous whose first name is 'Carol'", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Carol Burnett",
"votes": 75
},
{"name": "Carol Channing",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "Carole Lombard",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Carroll O'Connor",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Carol Lawrence",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Members of what occupation do you think spend a lot of time preening", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Modeling",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Acting",
"votes": 27
},
{"name": "Hairdressing",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Game Show Host",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Receptionist",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that comes out at night", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Moon",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Stars",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "Bats",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Owls",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Teeth",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an ingredient you put in an omelet", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Eggs",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Cheese",
"votes": 16
},
{"name": "Ham",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Green Pepper",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Milk",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Onions",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something for which you need a pail of water", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Wash Car",
"votes": 39
},
{"name": "Clean Floors",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Put Out Fire",
"votes": 12
},
{"name": "Wash Windows",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Water Plants",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that an interior decorator helps you pick out", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Curtains",
"votes": 46
},
{"name": "Wallpaper",
"votes": 21
},
{"name": "Furniture",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Colors",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Carpet",
"votes": 5
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something specific on a car that can be adjusted", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Mirror",
"votes": 34
},
{"name": "Seat",
"votes": 29
},
{"name": "Brakes",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Steering Wheel",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Seat Belt",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Radio",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something that always costs a lot to repair", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Car",
"votes": 75
},
{"name": "TV",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "House",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Refrigerator",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Watch",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "What do you always wind up saying to your kids on a long car trip?", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Be Quiet",
"votes": 38
},
{"name": "Almost There",
"votes": 24
},
{"name": "Sit Still",
"votes": 17
},
{"name": "Stop Fighting",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Take A Nap",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people eat while walking along the street", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Ice Cream",
"votes": 49
},
{"name": "Candy",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Hot Dog",
"votes": 20
},
{"name": "Popcorn",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Peanuts",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an occupation where you take the day's stress home with you", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Police Officer",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Physician",
"votes": 25
},
{"name": "Teacher",
"votes": 8
},
{"name": "Attorney",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Air Traffic Control",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Politician",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something a couple likes to have before they have children", 
"Answers": [{"name": "House",
"votes": 68
},
{"name": "Money",
"votes": 14
},
{"name": "Vacations",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Good Jobs",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Car",
"votes": 2
},
{"name": "Fun",
"votes": 2
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something wives try to get by nagging", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Money",
"votes": 35
},
{"name": "Help Around House",
"votes": 15
},
{"name": "Clothes",
"votes": 13
},
{"name": "A Night Out",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Their Way",
"votes": 6
},
{"name": "Attention",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Tell me something you think about women who wear glasses", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Smart",
"votes": 55
},
{"name": "Not Sexy",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Dull",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Librarian",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "School Teacher",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name an article of women's clothing once required, now optional", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hat",
"votes": 51
},
{"name": "Gloves",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Girdle",
"votes": 7
},
{"name": "Bra",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Scarf",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Slip",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name a place on your body where you'd find gold", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Hand",
"votes": 60
},
{"name": "Mouth",
"votes": 23
},
{"name": "Neck",
"votes": 9
},
{"name": "Ears",
"votes": 4
},
{"name": "Wrist",
"votes": 4
}
]},
{"Question": "Name someone or something you'd expect to see with Huck Finn", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Tom Sawyer",
"votes": 86
},
{"name": "Becky Thatcher",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Dog",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Injun Joe",
"votes": 3
},
{"name": "Jim",
"votes": 3
}
]},
{"Question": "Name something people say before going to bed", 
"Answers": [{"name": "Good Night",
"votes": 63
},
{"name": "Prayers",
"votes": 22
},
{"name": "I love You",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Sweet Dreams",
"votes": 5
},
{"name": "Turn Off Lights",
"votes": 2
}
]}
]